upfront group
Here we go...it's up-cami! This time with Beyonce, Mamoru Ameno, and Yukaon Yamazaki from Kawakami,
Beyonce, Mamoru Ameno, and Momohime Kiyama from Kawakami.
This program is a behind-the-scenes look at the production process of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you our recording, rehearsal and other production process.
Now, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs. I, Yamazaki, recently performed at the Thailand Japan Iconic Music Festival 2023.
Yes, you went to Thailand with Beyonce, didn't you? Yes, we did.
It was the first time for all of Beyonce to perform abroad, so I was really looking forward to it.
And we had a lot of people who always support us come to Thailand with us,
I think there were also many Thai people who saw us for the first time.
I am sure there are many Thai people who saw us for the first time, but they danced with us, called our names, and cheered and had fun together,
They were cheering and having fun together with us,
It made me very happy.
It was a lot of fun.
Everyone in Thailand looked at me with so many expressions on their faces,
It made me happy too,
I think I was able to put on a really nice smile.
I smiled a lot.
What do you think?
I, Kino, love Thai language so much that I studied it this time.
It was wonderful!
This was the third time in my life that I went to Thailand.
I have friends in Thailand and I really love the country,
But this time I finally realized that I don't speak Thai.
I realized it?
Now that I'm aware of it, I thought it would be nice to make my stay a little more convenient,
I studied for just a little bit, just 3 weeks really,
Thank you! Thank you!
When I was in Thailand for an interview or appeared on a TV program,
I was asked to speak in Thai, and I responded in Thai,
I also taught Thai to Beyonce members,
I taught the Beyonce members Thai, and we all said "Naramaika" together, which means "Is it cute in Thai? I asked them if they were cute in Thai,
It was a great memory for me,
It was a great memory for me, and I want to study more and become more fluent in Thai so that I can be more useful.
I really feel that Momohime-chan, Kiyo, was a great help to me this time,
I really appreciate your help.
I really feel like thank you.
Kopungkar!
I learned a lot of good things about Thailand, and I want to continue to spread the goodness of Thailand with Momohime-chan leading the way.
I hope we can go again with Beyonce.
Kop n Kha!
Let's start with this up-dated paper.
Tsubaki Factory It's my life Vocal Recording
From Tsubaki Factory's latest single released on September 27th,
Here's a sneak peek of the vocal recording session of Yumi Kasai, Yuuki it's my life.
You want to create a large scale image that everyone can sing together like this, don't you?
Yes.
Let's start with the A melody, shall we?
Photographs from last year, laughing at how young we are.
We acted like adults... but it's so sad...
Oh, you know...
Yes, that's right.
But with a little rhythm.
But it's so sadBut it's sad.
But it's so sad.
It's like...
No, it's not.
Start with "yes.
But it's sad.
Yeah, I see what you mean.
Yes.
Last year's photoshoot. We laughed about how young we were.
We were both so grown up. But it's so sad.
Yeah, it's perfect.
We're still in the first half of the A melody, so it's too soon to be happy.
I was really nervous.
Why should you be?
We've done it so many times.
This song is really hard to remember.
Don't worry about it.
Don't think too much.
Okay, let's continue.
The second half of the A melody.
You two act all grown up, but it's so sad.
Matching angled pieces
Memories are dazzling
It's a sign that we've come a long way.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's what I meant.
I'd like to bounce that first line a little more, though.I'd like to bounce the first line a bit more, though.
Matching angle piece
It's like...
Piece
Flutter, flutter, flutter, flutter, flutter, flutter
Matching angle piece
That's about right.
They look so grown up. But it's so sad.
Matching angle peace
The memories are dazzling.
We've come a long way.
Okay, perfect.
Let's try the B melody.
Let's do it again with a firm bounce
Let's do it again.
and the energy's too much in the future...
Okay, before you overthink it...
I'll give it a little more rock than a, but not too much armor, just enough to keep it fresh.
I'm just trying to keep the bounce a little more natural, because it's a little awkward right now, and the future is too energetic
I'm not going to overthink it...
I want to give it a nuance that says, "That's it," so...
Yes, yes, yes... it's got that kind of feel to it.
Yes...
I'll do that before I overthink it.
Before I overthink it, let's try serving it.
Before I overthink it
cat cat
Oh, no!
ANI.
The voice is nice, but the notes are getting longer. It's getting a little long. Tighter.
That's the accent.
Yeah, that's what I meant.
And the line after "okay" should be a little more nuanced.
Let's do it.
Accent that low.
Next time
OK, we're done!
Yay!
Thank you for your hard work!
Wow!
I really love your voice, as everyone has said,
I always listen to her voice, which is gentle but has a core to it, and I think it's really wonderful,
Also, when I watch the music videos, there are a lot of blue and light blue used in the music videos and the costumes,
I felt refreshed by the blue and light blue used in the music video and costumes.
Yes, the music is really sparkling and you can tell it's from Tsubaki Factory,
I thought it was a great fit for Yumi's voice.
I would like to hear it a lot at live performances.
That's all for Tsubaki Factory, Yuki, It's My Life, and Yumi Kasai's vocal recording!
TOPINOLE! It's my life! It doesn't matter what the end point is
Each one of them remembers their love
Tsubaki Factory, Yuuki! It's my life!
Let's work together!
Next up is JuiceJuice Funky Flashing Vocal RecordingNext up: JuiceJuice Funky Flashing Vocal Recording
Here is a look at the vocal recording of JuiceJuice's latest single, Funky Flashing, Numberlul.
Yes, yes, yes. Is there anything you don't understand? No, it's OK.
OK, let's start recording. Okay, let's go ahead and record.
Okay, let's start with the first three lines. Okay, let's start with the first three lines. Okay.
Okay.
Invite someone to come and listen.
Let's spend the night that's about to begin.
You'll never be alone in your room. You'll always be lonely.
Party night is just like a big dance party.
I'm thinking of inviting someone to a party where there's a lot of dancing.
Okay, here we go.
[ED]
♪ OK!
OK!
Okay! Let's go to the next block!
♪ Clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands ♪
Clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands.
You can dance to that girl's love song
Oh, let's play Wonderful music
Let's dance Disco till the wee hours
Let's make funky night
If you've heard it once
You'll forget it
Let's play Let's dance
Um, OK, you know what bass is?
Bass?
Dot-dot-dot-dot-dot-dot-dot... Dotzteratatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatatat
It's supposed to be delectic dotsutteretta.
Let's tarabeis teletta teletta
Telette telette telette telette telette
It's going to be "baisteretteretteretteretteretteretteretteretteretteretteretterette
I'm going to add this to the base of the song.
I'm going to start the song with a crawl, and then drop it down with a bang.
Let's tête-êt-êt-êt-êt-êt-êt-êt-êt-êt-êt-êt-êt
The "tette tette tette" part is like singing along with the bass.
And if you can get into the back of the song, you can make it more groovy.
Yes, I'll try it again.
Let's try one more time.
Let's try it again.
You can dance to it.
Oh, let's play Lovely Music
Let's dance Disco till the wee hours
Let's make funky night
Once you've heard it, you'll never forget it
Okay, okay, okay
Okay, let's go to the next back
I can feel the hope overflowing from here
You can sing this the same way you sang the first part.
And then, on a low beat, to her love song.
Okay.
[ED]
The hot things that overflow from my heart...
Did I do it?
It's okay if you say it in your own voice. It's totally fine if you say it out loud.
Shall we try it?
Yes, I will.
I can feel the passion overflowing from your heart.
Clap your hands, her love song
Okay.
Your partner, the one you didn't sing just now.
Yes, sir.
Get into the rhythm
Kuruchizu-san's hands, they'll be dancing in the morning
to the part where he says
I'm supposed to dance
Oh, oh, oh!
Yes!
From the heart!
It's overflowing!
I can feel the heat.
Ride the ritum.
Squeeze the tego
To the top of my lungs
You can step on the steps and you can dance
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Can you do the ahhhh?
Aaahhh!
Yeah, let's do it that way.
Okay, sorry, I'll do it again.
Aaaaaaah!
I'm sorry, I'll do it again.It's all gone awry.
What's that?
Aww...
Let's just do that part.
That part's good.
We can do the steps and dance.
Aww...
Yes, it's okay.
I think that's about right.
Okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
We had a two-man concert with Beyoncé and Juice Juice.
During the rehearsal, I was so amazed by Damballah's singing that I talked to him.
I said, "You're too good!
And he was like, "What are you talking about? And he was like, "What are you talking about?
I just thought it was too good to be true.
I was like...
I thought his voice was so beautiful, like a musical instrument, that I wanted to make it my ringtone.
I'm having such a luxurious time listening to it right now, and when I hear you sing, I get a kind of numb feeling, it's so cool.
I really love it, so I was happy to hear it a lot!
That's all for the vocal recording of JuiceJuice Funky Flash Dambaralulu!
I'm sure she'll be fine as she is!
Beyonce, Mamoru Ameno, Yukane Yamazaki of Kawakami and
Up-cam by Momohime Kiyama from Beyonce Amenomori Kawakami
Next, here we go!
Angelem Doukousei Vocal Recording
From Angulum's latest single From Angulum's latest single
Watch the vocal recording of the student Reira Ise, who is a member of the same band!
It's more inverted.
I can see it.
Like that girl, I'm sure everyone looks better than me
I don't show it when we play
Tsunku III's music is characterized by the way he cuts his songs with a lot of breath.
I felt that it's quite difficult to be conscious of the endings when the key is low, so I tried to keep my feelings low and keep the feeling in my body.
So I tried to keep the feeling in my body while keeping it low.
It's been quite a while since I've recorded with this kind of ending in mind, so I really struggled with that.
I think I struggled a lot with that.
Yes, I did.
Because, but...
Yes.
Yes, yes.
Finally.
Home.
I used to be so scared of betrayal if I trusted you.
You're genuinely kind, aren't you?
If I believe, if I believe
If you believe... if you believe...
Yes, I do
Thank you for watching.
I was afraid that if I trusted you, you'd betray me.I was afraid that if I trusted you, you would betray me.
You're genuinely kind
Though I was frightened of betrayal if I trusted you
The B melody is a place where the feeling gradually rises toward the chorus.
But it's not just the way the words end.
He gave me a lot of advice on how to accentuate the rhythm of the part I was singing.
So I sang the song with this in mind.
I love you.
I'm sorry I bought it.
I love you and I'm sorry
Yazahi
I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you
I love you I know how happy you've been
I know, I know, I know
Yes, I do.
No.
Yes.
I love you. I'm sorry I ever doubted you.
I love you I know how happy you were
You sing with a big smile on your face.
And to add a little color to my voice.
When I'm happy, when I'm having fun, when I'm happy, when I'm about to cry...
I think there are times when I feel like crying.
I think there are times when I feel like crying, or when I'm moved.
I'm very conscious of that while I'm singing.
I want to keep the rhythm of the song very important.
I want to keep the rhythm in mind as I sing the song, while valuing the emotion. It was very difficult because I had to think about both the emotion and the rhythm.
I had to think about both, so it was very difficult.
It's a great chorus, so I tried to be very conscious of that.
I'm sure they understood.
Yes, they do.
WEEP HEAD
I know you're happy.
We haven't sung a song where we were so conscious of the rhythm so much recently.
So it was a fresh recording with a slightly different feel from usual.
I think it's a song that will be important in the future.
I was able to sing the song with great care.
I'm very satisfied with the recording.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you very much.
It looks difficult. It looks difficult.
The rhythm, and the timing of cutting off the endings,
I'm really not good at cutting off the end of words,
I thought it was a very difficult song,
Also, I could see that Leila was really serious about this song,
It made me want to listen to it again. I want to listen to it again.
I was quite impressed by the way she counted the end of words with her hands,
I do that a lot, but when I am conscious of it in recording or something,
When I am conscious of it in recording, I am told that there are 5 endings, or 4 or 4 and a half endings,
But when I count like this, I don't know what I'm doing.
Leila is so determined,
But the end of the song is just right.
I was really impressed by the way she breathed out so beautifully. I thought to myself, "I don't think I could sing that. I thought I would never be able to sing. I thought I would do my best to get the rhythm right.
That's all for now.These are the vocal recordings of my angsty monk Ishereira.
Maybe it's the summer.
I wonder if it's a dream, or if I'm just a little emotionally unstable.
Whose fault is it?
Over! New single
Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer on sale now!
Thank you for all your hard work!
It's time to say goodbye to Yuhane Yamazaki and Momohime Kiyama.
I, Momohime Kiyama, was surprised to see how differently each group handles recording and what they say about it.
I was surprised to see how different the recording methods and the things they say are in different groups.
I thought that I really respected him a lot, because I don't receive such a high level of attention from him.
I, Yamazaki, saw Reina Ise's recording and was reminded of the importance of rhythm in Hello Project's songs.
I'd like to be more conscious of the importance of rhythm in Hello Project songs and Beyoncé's songs as well.
I also feel this when I cover Hello Project songs, so I want to continue to be conscious of it.
UpCami takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel so we can show you what you can't see in the real world!
This time upcami is with Yuhane Yamazaki of Beyons Ame no Mori Kawabini and Momohime Kiyama of Beyons Ame no Mori Kawabini!
Farewell!
Next time's up-sheet will be
From Tsubaki Factory's latest single
The recording of "Freedom if you're just delusional
and
the recording of "Ocha no Ma Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer" will be released!
Please look forward to it!